(Leonard:)So, what kind of cruise is this
you're going on?
(Mrs Cooper:)It's called
the Born Again Boat Ride.
(Mrs Cooper:)Christian Quarterly gave it
their highest rating: five thorny crowns.
(Mrs Cooper:)I do wish you'd come with me,
Sheldon.
Oh, well, Mom, if I did,
it would be conclusive proof...
(Sheldon:)...that your God can work miracles.
(Mrs Cooper:)You're missing out. It's gonna be
wall-to-wall fun. It's all themed.
There's Jonah-and-the-whale
watching.
All you can eat
Last Supper Buffet.
And my personal favorite,
Gunning with God.
(Leonard:)What's Gunning with God?
I'm afraid to ask, heh.
Oh, it is a hoot and a haIf.
(Mrs Cooper:)You write your sins
on a clay pigeon...
...they fire them up in the air, and you
pulverize them with a 12-gauge shotgun...
(Mrs Cooper:)...full of our Lord's forgiveness.
(Sheldon:)Frankly, Mom, I'm encouraged to see
how advanced your group has become...
(Sheldon:)...willing to sail out into the ocean
without fear of falling off the edge.